# Alfredo Adiyasa

# **Database Developer**

- 628551860540
- alfredo.adiyasa@gmail.com
- alfredooadi.github.io
- Tangerang, Indonesia

#### SUMMARY

I am a graduate of Informatics from Multimedia Nusantara University. Currently, I work at PT First Wap International as a Database Developer. I have an interest in Database Developer, Database Administrator, and Data Analyst. I open various opportunities especially in the Data field to learn and develop myself into a Data Expert.

#### EXPERIENCE

Database Developer 08/2023 - Present

PT First Wap International 7

- · Create migration script for schema and data changes.
- · Solve database issues.
- · Optimize and maintain the database.
- Discuss with System Architecture to design the effective database.
- Support for deployment at client site when needed.
- · Research and suggest the tools that can improve the database system.

**Teaching Staff Member** 07/2022 - 07/2023

PT Optima Solusindo Informatika 7

- Teach coding, design, and robotics practice for elementary school children computer subjects.
- · Planned and implemented integrated lessons to meet national standards.
- Prepared quizzes, tests and examinations to gauge how well students were learning.

Website Developer Intern 08/2021 - 11/2021

PT Lima Pilar ↗

- Create a Workee company profile website using the Laravel Framework.
- · Created powerful Content Management Systems to serve as interface for client.
- · Conducted unit testing to deliver optimal browser functionality.
- Troubleshooting code to find and resolve bugs.

## Website Developer Intern

08/2021 - 11/2021

TOUCHÉ Development Center 7

- Improved website functionality by redesigning, updating and implementing PHP codes, plug ins and extensions.
- Delivered project reports and milestone updates to supervisor.
- Conducted unit testing to deliver optimal browser functionality.
- Troubleshooting code to find and resolve bugs.
- Collaborate with developers, designers, web publishers, and producers to support revenue operations and meet project deadlines.

1/2

## EDUCATION

Information Technology 2018 - 2022

Multimedia Nusantara University - Bachelor of Computer Science

- Elected to Equipment Division for Maxima in 2019
- Member of UMN Medical Center

## CERTIFICATES

SQL (Intermediate) Certificate > 08/2023 - Present

HackerRank

MTA: HTML5 Application Development Fundamentals  $\Briangle$ 

Microsoft

10/2021 - Present

#### SKILLS

HTML and CSS Advanced Basic Java

PHP Microsoft Office Intermediate Advanced MySQL Advanced **Problem Solving** Advanced Intermediate Teamwork Linux Advanced **Bash Scripting** Intermediate Communication Expert

Intermediate

Python

## LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Intermediate